<items>
<item><author_id>vivimdelcuentu</author_id><item_type>content</item_type><item_id>c</item_id><description>Els Vivim del Cuentu som un grup de 8 rondallaires que vam néixer el desembre del 2006 per tal de fer arribar els contes i fer volar la imaginació a petits i grans d’arreu del país. Creiem en el poder dels contes per a educar, per a fer pensar i també, és clar, per a entretenir. Per això fa temps que creem i escrivim les nostres pròpies històries per apropar els infants a noves realitats.</description><language>Catala</language><date /><place /><link>https://www.vivimdelcuentu.org/</link></item>
<item><author_id>dario</author_id><item_type>commentary</item_type><item_id>3</item_id><media_id>c</media_id><description>Vivim del cuento. Serie de llibres infantils, basats en els classics de tota la vida. L'historia i sobretot la moraleja s'ha cambiat i actualitzat per als valors de l'actualitat. De longitud mitja i ben il·lustrats, la col·lecció consta de més de 20 números.</description><commentary>test_com</commentary><language>Catala</language><author>Vivim del cuentu</author><date /><place /><score>4</score><link /></item>
<item><author_id>Cuentasticos</author_id><item_type>content</item_type><item_id>d</item_id><description>Cuentásticos es un podcast de cuentos en español dirigido a familias con niños entre los cuatro y los doce años, que pone voces profesionales, música y efectos originales a las historias más ingeniosas y divertidas inspiradas por niños. Es un contenido original de calidad premium y una alternativa de entretenimiento libre de pantallas que despierta y estimula la imaginación, la creatividad y la apreciación por la diversidad cultural de nuestro idioma.</description><language>Español</language><date /><place/><link>https://cuentasticos.com/</link></item>
<item><author_id>dario</author_id><item_type>commentary</item_type><item_id>4</item_id><media_id>d</media_id><description>Cuentasticos. Podcast de cuentos infantiles originales y modernos. Con historias de 15 minutos de mucha fantasia. Un total de 9 capítulos. Las voces usan diferentes acentos del Español. Producción independiente entre Colombia y España. Perfecto para viajar en el coche con niños.</description><commentary>test_com</commentary><language>Español</language><author></author><date></date><place></place><score>4</score><link /></item>
<item><author_id>paulcooper</author_id><item_type>content</item_type><item_id>e</item_id><description>a history podcast looking at the collapse of a different civilization each episode. I want to ask: What did they have in common? Why did they fall? And what did it feel like to watch it happen? ​</description><language>English</language><date /><place/><link>https://fallofcivilizationspodcast.com/</link></item>
<item><author_id>dario</author_id><item_type>commentary</item_type><item_id>5</item_id><media_id>e</media_id><description>Fall of civilizations. Podcast sobre la história del auge y caida de civilizaciones antiguas. De gran detalle histórico y calidad narrativa. Larga duración entre una y cuatro horas en función del capítulo. Muy informativo y relajante. También disponible como videos, con el mismo sonido, usando imágenes de documentales y recreaciones históricas.</description><commentary>test_com</commentary><language>Inglés</language><author></author><date></date><place></place><score>5</score><link>http</link></item>
<item><author_id>Alex Hirsch</author_id><item_type>content</item_type><item_id>f</item_id><description>Gravity Falls is an American mystery comedy animated television series created by Alex Hirsch for Disney Channel and Disney XD. The series follows the adventures of Dipper Pines (Jason Ritter) and his twin sister Mabel (Kristen Schaal), who are sent to spend the summer with their great-uncle (or "Grunkle") Stan (Hirsch) in Gravity Falls, Oregon, a mysterious town full of paranormal incidents and supernatural creatures. The kids help Stan run the "Mystery Shack", the tourist trap that he owns, while also investigating the local mysteries. ​</description><language>Multiple</language><date /><place/><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gravity_Falls</link></item>
<item><author_id>dario</author_id><item_type>commentary</item_type><item_id>6</item_id><media_id>f</media_id><description>Gravity Falls. Serie de animación para adultos, que explica las aventuras de verano de un par de hermanos. Fantasía, aventuras y misterio. Puede que sea el mejor ejemplo del genero poppy-and-creepy, que se ha hecho popular (Hazbin hotel, Star contra las fuerzas del mal, The Owl House, ...)</description><commentary>test_com</commentary><language>English</language><author></author><date></date><place></place><score>5</score><link>http</link></item>
<item><author_id>Rudyard</author_id><item_type>content</item_type><item_id>g</item_id><description>"If—" is a poem by English poet Rudyard Kipling (1865–1936), written circa 1895[1] as a tribute to Leander Starr Jameson. It is a literary example of Victorian-era stoicism.[2] The poem, first published in Rewards and Fairies (1910) following the story "Brother Square-Toes", is written in the form of paternal advice to the poet's son, John.​</description><language>English</language><date /><place/><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/If%E2%80%94</link></item>
<item><author_id>dario</author_id><item_type>commentary</item_type><item_id>7</item_id><media_id>g</media_id><description>If. Poem about the basic human challenges, and what it takes to be a successful human being. Promotes perseverance and resilience. Engaging and epic.</description><commentary>test_com</commentary><language></language><author>Rudiyard Kipling</author><date></date><place></place><score>4</score><link>http</link></item>
<item><author_id>Ironhide</author_id><item_type>content</item_type><item_id>h</item_id><description>​Kingdom Rush is a 2011 tower defense game developed by Ironhide Game Studio and published by Armor Games. In the game's medieval fantasy setting, players take control of a general serving under King Denas of Linirea, who must defend the land from an onslaught of evil monsters. Each level is composed of a number of pre-set roads, which the player can place defensive towers around to fight off the approaching monsters. Slaying enemies gives the player gold, which they can use to buy new towers or upgrade existing ones to improve their capabilities. </description><language>English</language><date /><place/><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kingdom_Rush</link></item>
<item><author_id>dario</author_id><item_type>commentary</item_type><item_id>8</item_id><media_id>h</media_id><description>Kingdom Rush. Videojuego disponible para navegador o Android (mobil o tableta) del estilo "tower defense". Uno de los mejores y más elaborados ejemplos del género. Gratuito y adictivo. </description><commentary>test_com</commentary><language></language><author></author><date></date><place></place><score>3</score><link>http</link></item>
<item><author_id>Aaron</author_id><item_type>content</item_type><item_id>i</item_id><description>Korgoth of Barbaria is an American adult animated television pilot created by Aaron Springer, a storyboard artist, writer and director for Dexter's Laboratory, The Grim Adventures of Billy and Mandy, Samurai Jack, and SpongeBob SquarePants, who previously created another failed pilot at Cartoon Network Studios called Periwinkle Around the World. He would later go on to produce Billy Dilley's Super-Duper Subterranean Summer for Disney XD. Genndy Tartakovsky, creator of Dexter's Laboratory and Samurai Jack, directed the animation for the pilot. This was not the only time he worked on a pilot created by Springer, as Tartakovsky also produced and directed Periwinkle Around the World. It is the first Cartoon Network Studios production to be co-produced by Williams Street. ​</description><language>English</language><date /><place/><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Korgoth_of_Barbaria</link></item>
<item><author_id>dario</author_id><item_type>commentary</item_type><item_id>9</item_id><media_id>i</media_id><description>Korgoth of Barbaria. Pilot of a TV show that was never aired, about a barbarian's adventure in a typical fantasy sword-and-sorcery world. Comedy driven, brutal and unapologetic, makes fun of all the cliches of the genre, delivering a continuous entertainment.</description><commentary>test_com</commentary><language>English</language><author></author><date></date><place></place><score>4</score><link>http</link></item>
<item><author_id>Kurzgesagt</author_id><item_type>content</item_type><item_id>j</item_id><description>​Our core skill is telling stories about science and the world using different channels and media: we create elaborate videos based on detailed research about topics like space, technology, biology and society. We design products inspired by science like our posters and journals. And, last but not least, we develop fun interactive experiences in the form of apps and video games. We specialize in explaining complex topics in an approachable and holistic way. Our videos are based on rigorous research and use vibrant and fun vector illustrations and animation to transport impactful messages.</description><language>Multiple</language><date /><place/><link>https://kurzgesagt.org/</link></item>
<item><author_id>dario</author_id><item_type>commentary</item_type><item_id>10</item_id><media_id>j</media_id><description>Kurzgesagt. A series of animated videos, between 5 and 10 minutes long, about scientific phenomena, full of fun facts. Allows for the understanding and learning of complex concepts (black holes, human immune system, ...) in a simple and accessible way. Animation is beautiful and engaging. An excessive amount of videos seem overly focused on apocalyptic topics, as well as human mind, moving away from the original scientific grounding.  </description><commentary>test_com</commentary><language></language><author></author><date></date><place></place><score>4</score><link>http</link></item>
<item><author_id>Radiocontes</author_id><item_type>content</item_type><item_id>k</item_id><description>En una casa de turisme rural, un grup d’amics viuran un seguit de misteris i aventures. Ajudeu-los a resoldre els enigmes, i sentireu l’emoció de La casa del bosc.​</description><language>Catala</language><date /><place/><link>https://www.radiocontes.cat/la-casa-del-bosc/</link></item>
<item><author_id>dario</author_id><item_type>commentary</item_type><item_id>11</item_id><media_id>k</media_id><description>La Casa del Bosc. La casa del bosc es un podcast infantil de sis capitols de 20-25 minuts cadascún. Ideal per escoltar al cotxe, explica les aventures d'un grup de nens durant unes vacances. Les interpretacions son força bones, i embadaleix a nens de 4 a 12 anys. Us quedareu amb ganes de més.</description><commentary>test_com</commentary><language></language><author></author><date></date><place></place><score>4</score><link>http</link></item>
<item><author_id>lasotana</author_id><item_type>content</item_type><item_id>l</item_id><description>​La Sotana es un programa de humor irreverente sobre el Barça y el mundo del fútbol que se emite semanalmente en formato radiofónico. El programa, de una hora de duración, es producido y moderado por el gerundense Andreu Juanola, con los comentarios de Manel Vidal Boix, Joel Díaz y Modgi, y con Enric Gusó como técnico de sonido. </description><language>English</language><date /><place/><link>https://www.patreon.com/lasotana/home</link></item>
<item><author_id>dario</author_id><item_type>commentary</item_type><item_id>12</item_id><media_id>l</media_id><description>La Sotana. Podcast sobre l'actualitat del Barça, en clau d'humór. Irreverent i ofensiu, amb mencions frequents a temes delicats i éticament delicats. Busca constantment els limits del humor, i no te altre vocació que l'entreteniment. D'una hora de duració, inclou amb frequencia convidats de l'orbita del esport, alguns d'ells del máxim nivell protagonista.</description><commentary>test_com</commentary><language></language><author></author><date></date><place></place><score>4</score><link>http</link></item>
<item><author_id>pbs</author_id><item_type>content</item_type><item_id>m</item_id><description>Join hosts Michelle Barboza-Ramirez, Kallie Moore, and Blake de Pastino as they take you on a journey through the history of life on Earth. From the dawn of life in the Archaean Eon through the Mesozoic Era — the so-called “Age of Dinosaurs” -- right up to the end of the most recent Ice Age. ​</description><language>English</language><date /><place/><link>https://www.pbs.org/show/eons/</link></item>
<item><author_id>dario</author_id><item_type>commentary</item_type><item_id>13</item_id><media_id>m</media_id><description>PBS Eons. A series of videos about paleontology. Between 5 and 15 minutes long, these provide a scientifically based, but accessible explanation to an interesting fact or curious event of Earth's distant past. Topics regard ancient ecology, flora and fauna. And dinosaurs. Lots of dinosaurs.</description><commentary>test_com</commentary><language></language><author></author><date></date><place></place><score>4</score><link>http</link></item>
<item><author_id>don</author_id><item_type>content</item_type><item_id>n</item_id><description>Rejected is a 2000 animated surrealist short comedy film directed by Don Hertzfeldt that was released in 2000. It was nominated for an Academy Award for Best Animated Short Film the following year at the 73rd Academy Awards,[1] and received 27 awards from film festivals around the world.​</description><language>English</language><date /><place/><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rejected</link></item>
<item><author_id>dario</author_id><item_type>commentary</item_type><item_id>14</item_id><media_id>n</media_id><description>Rejected. A short movie, about 10 min., showing a series of absurd sketches about alienation and mental decay. Fun and disturbing. Very original. </description><commentary>test_com</commentary><language></language><author></author><date></date><place></place><score>4</score><link>http</link></item>
<item><author_id>eyezmaze</author_id><item_type>content</item_type><item_id>o</item_id><description>​This is a kind of evolved whack-a-mole game. ah, a kind of action game or like that. Well, you can save money and buy items you want. Let's challenge the unlimitedly coming out Tontie with your powered hammer. There are 20 stages with flock of ideas. Can you defeat the last boss? Using the numeric keypad. Each number corresponds the hole Tontie appears. 0 key is a pause button.</description><language>English</language><date /><place/><link>https://www.eyezmaze.com/flash/tontieV1.html</link></item>
<item><author_id>dario</author_id><item_type>commentary</item_type><item_id>15</item_id><media_id>o</media_id><description>Tontie. Videojuego muy simple basado en el teclado numerico, del estilo whack-a-mole. Reto de concentración y velocidad de reacción con muchos niveles de dificultad. Bastante adictivo, adecuado para ganar agilidad mental y velocidad con los dedos.</description><commentary>test_com</commentary><language></language><author></author><date></date><place></place><score>4</score><link>http</link></item>
<item><author_id>nick</author_id><item_type>content</item_type><item_id>p</item_id><description>The Wrong Trousers is a 1993 British stop-motion animated short film co-written and directed by Nick Park, featuring his characters Wallace and Gromit, and was produced by Aardman Animations in association with Wallace and Gromit Ltd., BBC Bristol, Lionheart Television and BBC Children's International. It is the second film featuring the eccentric inventor Wallace (voiced by Peter Sallis) and his dog Gromit, following A Grand Day Out (1989). In the film, a villainous penguin, Feathers McGraw, posing as a lodger, recruits Wallace by using his techno-trousers to steal a diamond from the city museum. ​</description><language>English</language><date /><place/><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Wrong_Trousers</link></item>
<item><author_id>dario</author_id><item_type>commentary</item_type><item_id>16</item_id><media_id>p</media_id><description>Wrong Trousers. Short, about 30 min. long, stop-motion animated movie about a man and his dog, who host a penguin who turns out to be a criminal mastermind. Ideal for kids and adults alike, fun and visually appealing.</description><commentary>test_com</commentary><language></language><author></author><date></date><place></place><score>4</score><link>http</link></item>
</items>